Something I see quite often in the comments under interviews that I do are folks who consider themselves foundational black Americans saying Amanda Seals is not an FBA.
She's not an ADOS. She doesn't speak for us.
So first, let me just say that my father and I are both descendants of chattel slavery in the United States.
But what I want to also add is you're right.
And I don't speak for you. I don't speak for anybody. I speak for myself.
However, even if I were someone out here with a platform and with the opportunity to advocate, I want to know what it is that you feel I am saying that is counterproductive to your goals as a foundational black American.
What am I doing that is antithetical to your wants as a foundational black American?
Because as far as I'm concerned, anybody who is centering reparations, who is centering the actual efforts to dismantle government systems that use foundational black Americans instead of being useful to foundational black Americans.
And anyone who is constantly acknowledging not only the empowering, not only the empowering, the education, but the preservation of identity of not just black Americans, but of the diaspora.
Anyone doing that to me is somebody that even if you didn't feel was a member of your group that you would be lifting up.
Now, if you disagree with acknowledging that there is a diaspora of black folks that exists not only within the United States, but outside the United States that are bound together in our blackness.
Then we fundamentally disagree, but regardless, I want all of you FBA-ers to know that when you find yourself in the comments saying, Amanda Seals is not an FBA, she doesn't speak for us.
You are not hurting my feelings, you are hurting your efforts because you are ostracizing someone who wants nothing more than the black people of the United States and of the world to be acknowledged and to be given our just due.